<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
  <title>VaaS Solutions | News Marketplace</title>
  <link>https://vaas.solutions</link>
  <description>Latest premium publications, events, and media news from VaaS Solutions.</description>
  <language>en-us</language>
  <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 16:10:03 GMT</lastBuildDate>
  <atom:link href="https://vaas.solutions/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Impact Excellence Awards 2026]]></title>
    <link>https://vaas.solutions/events/impact-excellence-awards-2026-98f9db73-b7b3-4b0c-b993-3635cadefc93</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://vaas.solutions/events/impact-excellence-awards-2026-98f9db73-b7b3-4b0c-b993-3635cadefc93</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[A prestigious awards gala in Dubai honoring global leaders and high achievers from diverse industries who excelled in performance, innovation, and impact. Winners are selected through nominations, interviews, and jury evaluation, culminating in a high-profile ceremony.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 18:28:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sikka Art & Design Festival 2026]]></title>
    <link>https://vaas.solutions/events/sikka-art--design-festival-2026-bf5caa7c-1cde-4348-85f1-4ecb656dba62</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://vaas.solutions/events/sikka-art--design-festival-2026-bf5caa7c-1cde-4348-85f1-4ecb656dba62</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[A vibrant cultural festival in Dubai showcasing Emirati, UAE and GCC artists through art installations, murals, exhibitions, workshops, performances and interactive experiences across the historic Al Shindagha neighbourhood.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 18:27:59 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Shoptalk Luxe Middle East 2026 – Abu Dhabi]]></title>
    <link>https://vaas.solutions/events/shoptalk-luxe-middle-east-2026--abu-dhabi-9964a196-388d-46a3-981a-73f994bd0f43</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://vaas.solutions/events/shoptalk-luxe-middle-east-2026--abu-dhabi-9964a196-388d-46a3-981a-73f994bd0f43</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Shoptalk Luxe Middle East 2026 marks the inaugural Middle East edition of Shoptalk Luxe, bringing together the world’s most influential luxury retail leaders, brands, and innovators. Hosted in Abu Dhabi, this three-day flagship event will convene over 2,000 senior decision-makers and 170+ global speakers from luxury retail, fashion, hospitality, and technology.

The conference will focus on redefining luxury commerce through experience-led retail, omnichannel transformation, AI-driven personalisation, leadership excellence, and next-generation consumer engagement. Hosted at the iconic Emirates Palace, the event combines high-level insights, curated networking, and executive-level experiences in one of the world’s most prestigious luxury destinations.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 10:14:19 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Sharjah Entrepreneurship Festival (SEF) 2026 – Where We Belong]]></title>
    <link>https://vaas.solutions/events/sharjah-entrepreneurship-festival-sef-2026--where-we-belong-9817cd18-82b7-402e-a612-bc30d85cf8c8</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://vaas.solutions/events/sharjah-entrepreneurship-festival-sef-2026--where-we-belong-9817cd18-82b7-402e-a612-bc30d85cf8c8</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Sharjah Entrepreneurship Festival (SEF) 2026 returns for its landmark ninth edition as the largest entrepreneurship and innovation gathering in the Middle East. Organized by the Sharjah Entrepreneurship Center (Sheraa), SEF 2026 will welcome over 14,000 attendees, 300+ global speakers, startups, investors, creatives, and ecosystem leaders from across the world.

Held under the theme “Where We Belong”, the festival celebrates community as the engine of innovation, spotlighting how entrepreneurs can create meaningful impact through collaboration, creativity, and purpose-driven leadership. The two-day festival features inspirational keynote talks, investor meetings, startup showcases, masterclasses, pitch competitions, and immersive themed zones covering technology, creativity, impact, wellbeing, and scaling businesses.

Hosted at Sharjah Research, Technology and Innovation Park (SRTIP), SEF 2026 positions Sharjah as a global benchmark for entrepreneurship, innovation, and knowledge-driven economic growth.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 11:59:34 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[World Governments Summit 2026]]></title>
    <link>https://vaas.solutions/events/world-governments-summit-2026-f9b843a7-f48b-4c8e-bdb3-63d2d73bbe83</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://vaas.solutions/events/world-governments-summit-2026-f9b843a7-f48b-4c8e-bdb3-63d2d73bbe83</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[In 2026, the World Governments Summit will convene under the theme &#39;Shaping Future Governments.&#39; This Summit will bring together governments, international organizations, thought leaders, and private sector leaders from around the globe to foster international cooperation and identify innovative solutions for future challenges, ultimately inspiring and empowering the next generation of governments.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 18:27:58 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[DDX'26 Dubai - UX & Innovation - Conference]]></title>
    <link>https://vaas.solutions/events/ddx26-dubai---ux--innovation---conference-02c2edb3-792c-4ff1-9648-73a10b5078e2</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://vaas.solutions/events/ddx26-dubai---ux--innovation---conference-02c2edb3-792c-4ff1-9648-73a10b5078e2</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Following the incredible success of DDX&#39;25 Dubai, we&#39;re thrilled to announce our return in February 2026! Join us for another transformative conference featuring the best minds in design, innovation, and technology. Stay tuned for details. This is where ideas shape the future! What to Expect: Inspiring Talks, Interactive Workshops, Networking Opportunities, Startup Awards.

Registration Charges: AED 679.00 / USD 190.00]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 18:27:58 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[STEP Conference Dubai 2026]]></title>
    <link>https://vaas.solutions/events/step-conference-dubai-2026-1b4fa6cd-2cef-4c82-ba0e-d3ca16450ae1</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://vaas.solutions/events/step-conference-dubai-2026-1b4fa6cd-2cef-4c82-ba0e-d3ca16450ae1</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Step began as a series of intimate workshops and gatherings and has evolved over 13 years into the leading tech festival in Dubai. Step Dubai 2026 marks the 14th edition of the festival – bringing together thousands of founders, investors, creatives, and tech enthusiasts from around the world. Under the theme “Intelligence Everywhere: The AI Economy,” Step 2026 explores how artificial intelligence is transforming every layer of our lives.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 18:27:59 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[TEDxUniversity of Birmingham Dubai]]></title>
    <link>https://vaas.solutions/events/tedxuniversity-of-birmingham-dubai-bf11639f-8dda-4132-81a6-057ec23b24b7</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://vaas.solutions/events/tedxuniversity-of-birmingham-dubai-bf11639f-8dda-4132-81a6-057ec23b24b7</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[This TEDx event is an independently organized TED experience where local speakers and thought leaders share powerful ideas worth spreading. It features live talks and curated presentations designed to spark conversation, connect communities, and inspire new perspectives across diverse topics.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 18:27:58 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Saudi Event Awards 2026]]></title>
    <link>https://vaas.solutions/events/saudi-event-awards-2026-38671ce3-6989-485c-a5f2-3fa84b72e269</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://vaas.solutions/events/saudi-event-awards-2026-38671ce3-6989-485c-a5f2-3fa84b72e269</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[The Saudi Event Awards honours excellence, innovation, and outstanding achievement in the events, entertainment, and MICE industry across Saudi Arabia, celebrating the best individuals, teams, agencies, suppliers, and venues shaping the Kingdom’s events ecosystem.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 18:27:59 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title><![CDATA[Dubai International Film Festival]]></title>
    <link>https://vaas.solutions/events/dubai-international-film-festival-5e447abd-502e-4d2c-8187-1843cb69109c</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://vaas.solutions/events/dubai-international-film-festival-5e447abd-502e-4d2c-8187-1843cb69109c</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[DIFF is the leading film festival in the UAE and one of the most influential in the Arab region, celebrating international and Arab cinema with screenings, industry seminars, red-carpet premieres, workshops, and awards honoring filmmaking excellence.]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 18:27:59 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
</channel>
</rss>